Yoo-hoo!
I'm going to go sightseeing in Kyoto from now on.
This time, we're going to divide the group into three, and the first group is this
The first group is this one: Yuki, ShiYuka, and Miyu!
We are going to do various sightseeing!
I'm off!
Here we go! Bus!
Here comes the bus!
I'm going to Arashiyama this summer!
Bye bye!
They're here!
It's here!
Yay!
Looks like so much fun!
Look at them, each one is really, really big!
They look so sweet!
Ready, go!
That's great! Second one to go!
Aren't they so shiny?
Bon appétit!
Won't it melt?
We did it, we did it, we did it.
I did it, I did it, I did it.
I did it. I did it. I did it.
I've got it.
I did it.
Yes, Shilka, after me.
The second one.
I'm scared.
Let's go.
So...
Now you're standing in the stormy mountains.
Yay!
It's getting cooler all the time.
It's cooler now.
The air feels so different.
The air is so clean.
I'm going to take a lot of pictures.
See you later.
See you.
Your hair is a little messed up, isn't it?
Chikmin.
Yah!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You look like a kid!
Like a bunny!
He's a turtle!
Thank you for your hard work!
Ta-da!
Congratulations!
Cheers!
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious!
You just went to the monkey park today.
What's that?
It's 3:36 p.m.
36 minutes?
Oh, come on!
What?
4:00 p.m.!
You think we're gonna make it in time for the rush?
You had all day to play and you only had an hour and a half.
We can't play for 30 minutes.
But we can play for 15 minutes.
No, what are you gonna do?
No, no, no.
I was really looking forward to it.
But I think we're getting a little too close, don't you? This.
Obviously. We should've gone first.
So, what do we do now? Go? Come on.
Let's go. Okay, I'll say I'm lost.
I'll go.
One time, one time.
You think we can go?
Do you think we can go?
We're in. Thank God! We made it!
Just in time for the monkey park! We made it!
We made it!
That's great! Just like that!
Oh, you're so cute!
What?
Oh, shit!
It's got Shizu on it.
That's awesome. That's awesome.
It's hard to walk on the summit.
Everyone in front.
This is so high.
We're at the monkey park, and I didn't expect it to take 20 minutes to get to the summit.
There's continuous destruction all the way up.
We're in the way of the mountain.
I don't know what I've been doing
I came here to see the monkeys.
The bottom of the mountain is hiking.
But this is about fitness.
Yes, it does.
Hang on to the positive, it's almost up, up, up.
It's like this, it's 20 minutes to the top of the mountain
I'll do my best to climb up to where I can see the monkeys
We're at the monkey park!
I'm not in the park, I'm in the park.
It really is.
There's all kinds of stuff all over the place.
And when you look behind you, it's a spectacular view!
Look at this.
A little bit of the city.
Hey, the mouth has just risen.
You can't see the whole view.
I'm a little tired.
It was really close.
I didn't think I'd be able to see the monkeys so straight.
I'm so satisfied and high
It's amazing!
The banana I wanted to photograph the most.
Yeah, bananas.
I want to take a banana picture!
Okay, I'm going to go have fun after this.
Yay!
One more time.
Wow.
Camera shot.
Let's go.
There you go.
Wow.
That was really good.
Oh, thank God.
Anyway, I'm just gonna make a phone call and then I'm gonna go drink too much Coco.
It's nice to meet you.
Maybe it's because you're beautiful. I'm nothing like you.
I'm nothing like you.
How's it look?
Oh! Hello?
I'm sorry, what are you doing?
Is everything okay?
Can we do the Mello Yello tour?
Three, two, one.
Ta-da!
What do you think?
How's it going?
Isn't it great?
And we have a special guest!
Special guest!
Mr. Otsuru.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look at the summary.
We don't have books to sing.
We are
I want you
I miss you
I'm so happy to see you
I can't catch my breath
monkey park in alacia
I don't know what's going on.
I'm scared
Oh, no!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What is it? Did I do it?
It's so fucked up.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
It's over here! It's over here! It's over here!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, that girl.
What?
What do I do?
I got something.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Come here, come here, come here.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
No, no, no!
Push, push, push your eyes
Both, both, now
Both both both
Only messed up
Oh, no.
Oh, no, I couldn't get it.
The one in the back...
The hardest one.
Oh, there they are.
I'm getting it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, it's so good. It's so good.
This is super good.
No, again.
Yutchan is amazing!
Next time it'll change color.
Oh, no, wait!
He's mad at me.
Thank you for watching.